High School Honor Student by Day. Hollywood Hooker by Night.
Angel is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Robert Vincent O'Neil.
Molly Stewart, a teen at the top of her class who survives by working nights as a prostitute on Hollywood Blvd, finds her
world beginning to fall apart when a depraved, necrophiliac serial killer begins targeting LA’s streetwalkers.
Lt. Andrews, played by Cliff Gorman.
Solly Mosler, played by Susan Tyrrell.
Mae, played by Dick Shawn.
Kit Carson, played by Rory Calhoun.
Molly Stewart / Angel, played by Donna Wilkes.
The Killer, played by John Diehl.
Angel is a 1984 American exploitation thriller film directed by
Robert Vincent O'Neil, written by O'Neil and Joseph M.
Cala, and starring Cliff Gorman, Susan Tyrrell, Dick
Shawn, Rory Calhoun, and Donna Wilkes.
The film follows a teenage prostitute in Los Angeles who faces danger when a
serial killer begins stalking and murdering her colleagues.
Released by New World Pictures, it was the first
installment in the Angel film series.
The film explores themes of high school,
prostitute, detective, exploitation, money.
The tone is intense.